"Blue Lips"
(Episode 8)
Did you guys sleep together last night?
I already told you.
I'm not interested in men.
Fine.
I see you're refusing the easy way out,
so you gotta go the hard way.
Hey, buddy.
Violence doesn't solve anything.
Let's talk this out calmly.
This is none of your business.
Stay out of it.
Xiao Wu is my friend.
His business
is my business.
You don't need to explain anything to him.
What exactly happened?
Let me help you figure this out.
Come on.
My boyfriend cheated on me.
And the guy was wearing blue lipstick.
Blue lipstick, sure.
But his hat is pulled down so low,
you can't even see his face.
What day of the week did you take this?
Last Wednesday.
That explains it.
Xiao Wu here
doesn't sing at the Blue
Moon Bar on Wednesdays.
Everyone at the bar can vouch for that.
You said your boyfriend
went out with someone from the bar.
Then it definitely wasn't Xiao Wu.
Fine.
If you're lying to me,
you'll pay for it.
Are you okay?
I don't even know the guy
he was just talking about.
I...
I know.
You're not into men, right?
I have to praise you.
You did well today.
You actually defended yourself,
and didn't even throw a punch.
No...
from now on at the bar,
things like this will happen more and more.
Fighting won't solve the problem.
Stop always trying to fight people.
What is your brain for?
What is your mouth for?
Learn to use them.
It's not like you won't be around anymore.
Are you going to stop
looking out for me?
That's not what I meant.
What I mean is,
you can't always count on me.
I'm not going to be by your side 24/7.
What will you do when I'm not around?
You need to be able to
solve problems on your own.
That's how you can better protect yourself.
Right?
Dummy.
Xiao Wu.
You're here so early today.
We haven't even opened yet.
Did Brother Mo
leave with you yesterday?
Why?
Nothing really.
It's just that when we
were closing up yesterday,
he came looking for you.
He didn't see you,
and even asked me about it.
Then,
I turned around and he was gone.
So I just wanted to ask you.
Are you and Brother Mo
really together?
No.
What's there to be shy about?
We can all see it.
Wait.
You guys?
Who else?
Well, me,
Xiao Fu,
Xiao Lee,
Ah Yuan...
A lot of people.
I mean,
Brother Mo hangs out here every single day.
If you ask him, he won't admit it,
but who couldn't tell?
Well,
maybe he just
likes coming here to
drink and listen to music.
Would he pay your damages just
for drinking and listening to music?
Damages?
What damages?
You didn't know?
Remember last time
when Brother Hao came and caused a scene?
You guys got into a fight.
Originally,
you and Brother Hao were supposed to
split the cost of the damages.
But Brother Mo paid your share.
He said he was involved in the fight too,
So he covered the cost?
You really didn't know?
Then I've said too much.
How much did he pay?
Not that much.
Guan Zhenghao was supposed
to pay the lion's share anyway.
But,
Brother Mo is really good to you.
He's so protective of you.
I've known him for a long time,
and I've never seen him with any friends.
He's always been a lone wolf.
I really didn't expect
he'd go this far for you.
What's up?
Here to buy Vandacon?
It's not time yet, is it?
What's this about?
These things are too expensive.
I can't accept them.
Besides,
the compensation for the fight
shouldn't have been paid by you.
We both got into that fight.
It's not right to make you pay for it all.
The phone and watch
haven't even been opened.
I wouldn't feel right keeping them.
What about the money?
You're still so short on cash.
Where did this money come from?
That's none of your business.
Where's your guitar?
I sold it.
Why did you sell it?
Just to pay me back?
Haven't I told you that I...
I know.
You said it.
With our relationship,
it's only natural for you
to spend money on me.
But I don't want our relationship
to be so deeply tied to money.
What do you mean?
You want to settle the score with me?
I just don't want to owe you too much.
Because I'm afraid I won't
be able to pay you back.
I don't need you to pay me back.
I did it willingly.
Really?
Then why did you spend so much money on me?
I...
It's because...
Because of what?
Is it just because
you want to sleep with me?
Right?
Well, if you don't want
these things, then fine.
I'm leaving.
I still have a gig at Blue Moon.
How are you going to
play without your guitar?
The guitar is gone,
but I'm still here.
Besides,
no one will complain
about the noise anymore.
Wait a minute.
This is a women's watch.
It's of no use to me.
I don't know who to give it to.
You keep it.
Or throw it away.
What's wrong?
You're not at the shop.
Just wandering the streets alone.
Bored.
Getting some fresh air.
You're in a bad mood.
Get in.
I happen to be in a bad mood too.
Let's chat.
Just looking at you,
I can tell you're troubled by love.
But I'm in no position to judge.
So?
You get troubled by love too?
Back then, I just couldn't let it go.
I kept the person,
but couldn't keep their heart.
I ended up making a total fool of myself.
It's better to just let go.
There's no need to
drag it out for too long.
Here.
Hello?
Are you free today?
I want to see you.
I don't think I can today.
What about later tonight?
Shixian.
Who's calling?
The bar owner.
Asking if I can work tonight.
Hello?
I really can't make it today.
What about tomorrow?
Probably not for the next couple of days.
Okay.
Wu Shixian.
I want to ask you a question.
In your eyes,
what exactly am I to you?
A...
really good...
brother.
Never mind.
I'll let you go.
I won't bother you anymore.
I'm hanging up.
Shixian.
Let's go.
Ah Heng.
Do me a favor.
I'll be busy lately, so I
won't be coming around.
Help me give this
to Wu Shixian.
What is this?
A cash gift.
Seriously?
I'm kidding.
You believe everything I say.
I was gonna say.
He's so cool,
there's no way he'd get married this young.
Any message you want me to pass on?
Tell him to live a good life.
Hello?
What?
Which hospital?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Doctor,
how is she?
Sudden syncope in patients with pulmonary
arterial hypertension is a normal occurrence.
She's stabilized now.
However,
the patient is showing
signs of right heart failure,
which needs to be taken very seriously.
This episode was triggered
by chronic fatigue and a cold.
It's still quite dangerous.
The patient has been relying on
medication for treatment, right?
Yes.
Given her current condition,
medication alone probably won't be enough.
You should take her to a
major hospital's outpatient clinic
for a thorough examination.
There are many types of
pulmonary arterial hypertension.
You need to see a specialist as soon as
possible to determine the exact classification.
Okay.
I understand.
I remember what you like to drink.
Wait for me a sec.
Xiao Wu.
This...
Brother Mo gave this to you.
When did he give it to you?
The day before yesterday.
You weren't here then,
so he asked me to...
Where is he?
I don't know.
He said...
you should live a good life.
Hello.
The number you have dialed
is temporarily unavailable.
Teng Mo.
Get up.
It's time to change the sheets.
There's no rush.
Let me hold you a little longer.
Shixian.
Don't trust anyone from now on.
People nowadays
might look decent on the outside,
but they're rotten to
the core on the inside.
Including me.
I'm not as good as you think.
You've been talking
weirdly for a while now.
Are these your dying words?
What are you talking about?
I just think you're sweet,
and I care about you.
This is for you.
What is this?
Look at it when you get back.